(function(){const s=document.createElement("link").relList;if(s&&s.supports&&s.supports("modulepreload"))return;for(const o of document.querySelectorAll('link[rel="modulepreload"]'))l(o);new MutationObserver(o=>{for(const i of o)if(i.type==="childList")for(const m of i.addedNodes)m.tagName==="LINK"&&m.rel==="modulepreload"&&l(m)}).observe(document,{childList:!0,subtree:!0});function p(o){const i={};return o.integrity&&(i.integrity=o.integrity),o.referrerpolicy&&(i.referrerPolicy=o.referrerpolicy),o.crossorigin==="use-credentials"?i.credentials="include":o.crossorigin==="anonymous"?i.credentials="omit":i.credentials="same-origin",i}function l(o){if(o.ep)return;o.ep=!0;const i=p(o);fetch(o.href,i)}})();const S=[{id:1,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",options:["Standard notation","Tab notation","Morse code notation","Graphics notation"],answer:"Morse code notation",category:"music"},{id:2,question:"What is the most common time signature in classical music?",options:["3/4","4/4","5/4","6/8"],answer:"4/4",category:"music"},{id:3,question:"Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",options:["Violin","Piano","Harp","Theremin"],answer:"Theremin",category:"music"},{id:4,question:"What is the most common key in pop music?",options:["C Major","G Major","D Major","A Major"],answer:"C Major",category:"music"},{id:5,question:"Which of the following is not a type of chord?",options:["Major","Minor","Diminished","Flat"],answer:"Flat",category:"music"},{id:6,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",options:["Jazz","Blues","Rock","Applesauce"],answer:"Applesauce",category:"music"},{id:7,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",options:["Harmony","Counterpoint","Form","Cooking"],answer:"Cooking",category:"music"},{id:8,question:"What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",options:["Allegro","Andante","Adagio","Moderato"],answer:"Allegro",category:"music"},{id:9,question:"Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",options:["Sonata","Symphony","Concerto","Spaghetti"],answer:"Spaghetti",category:"music"},{id:10,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",options:["Sibelius","Finale","MuseScore","Microsoft Word"],answer:"Microsoft Word",category:"music"}],k=[{id:11,question:"Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:12,question:"Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Futurism","Cubism"],answer:"Cubism",category:"modern-art"},{id:13,question:"Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:14,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",options:["Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Edvard Munch","Claude Monet"],answer:"Edvard Munch",category:"modern-art"},{id:15,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Fauvism","Cubism"],answer:"Fauvism",category:"modern-art"},{id:16,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",options:["Impressionism","Futurism","Surrealism","Abstract Expressionism"],answer:"Futurism",category:"modern-art"},{id:17,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",options:["Claude Monet","Paul Cezanne","Paul Gauguin","Paul Klee"],answer:"Claude Monet",category:"modern-art"},{id:18,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",options:["Henri Matisse","Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Pablo Picasso"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:19,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",options:["Claude Mone","Paul Cezanne","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:20,question:"Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",options:["Auguste Rodin","Alexander Calder","Jean Arp","Henry Moore"],answer:"Auguste Rodin",category:"modern-art"}],E=[{id:21,question:"What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",options:["if (condition):","if condition","if: condition","if condition:"],answer:"if condition:",category:"coding"},{id:22,question:"Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",options:["String","Number","Boolean","ArrayList"],answer:"ArrayList",category:"coding"},{id:23,question:"Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",options:["var","let","const","int"],answer:"int",category:"coding"},{id:24,question:"What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",options:["for i = 0 to 10","for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)","for (int i = 0; i <= 10)","for i in range(0, 10)"],answer:"for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",category:"coding"},{id:25,question:"Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",options:["while","for","do-while","foreach"],answer:"foreach",category:"coding"},{id:26,question:"Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",options:["+","-","*","$"],answer:"$",category:"coding"},{id:27,question:"In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"Python",category:"coding"},{id:28,question:"What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",options:["function name()","def name","function name","def name()"],answer:"def name()",category:"coding"},{id:29,question:"Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",options:["Int","String","Double","Object"],answer:"Object",category:"coding"},{id:30,question:"In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"C++",category:"coding"}],A={music:S,modernArt:k,coding:E},y=A,M=y.music.filter(a=>a.category==="music"),W=y.modernArt.filter(a=>a.category==="modern-art"),P=y.coding.filter(a=>a.category==="coding");document.getElementById("musicBtn").addEventListener("click",function(){w(M)});document.getElementById("artBtn").addEventListener("click",function(){w(W)});document.getElementById("codingBtn").addEventListener("click",function(){w(P)});function w(a){let s=0,p=0,l=0;function o(){let e=a[s],c=document.createElement("div");c.innerHTML=`
    <div class="quiz-container"><h2 class="quiz-header">Question ${s+1}</h2><p id="question">${e.question}</p>
    <ul>
      <li>
        <input type="radio" name="option" class="radiogroup" style="cursor: pointer" id="${e.options[0]}" value="${e.options[0]}"/> ${e.options[0]}
      </li>
      <li>
        <input type="radio" name="option" class="radiogroup" style="cursor: pointer" id="${e.options[1]}" value="${e.options[1]}"/> ${e.options[1]}
      </li>
      <li>
        <input type="radio" name="option" class="radiogroup" style="cursor: pointer" id="${e.options[2]}" value="${e.options[2]}"/> ${e.options[2]}
      </li>
      <li>
        <input type="radio" name="option" class="radiogroup" style="cursor: pointer" id="${e.options[3]}" value="${e.options[3]}"/> ${e.options[3]}
      </li>
    </div>`,document.getElementById("main").innerHTML="",document.getElementById("main").appendChild(c);let r=document.createElement("button");r.innerHTML="Back",r.addEventListener("click",v),document.getElementById("main").appendChild(r);let t=document.createElement("button");t.innerHTML="Next",t.addEventListener("click",m),document.getElementById("main").appendChild(t);let n=document.querySelectorAll(".radiogroup");for(let d=0;d<n.length;d++)n[d].addEventListener("click",i)}function i(e){let c=e.target,r=document.querySelectorAll(".radiogroup");for(let t=0;t<r.length;t++)r[t]!==c&&(r[t].disabled=!0)}function m(){let e=document.querySelector("input[name='option']:checked"),c=document.getElementById("question").innerText;if(e){l=e.value;let r=a[s],t={question:c,answer:l},n=[],d=localStorage.getItem("userAnswer");if(d){n=JSON.parse(d);let g=!1;for(let u=0;u<n.length;u++)if(n[u].question==c){n[u].answer=l,g=!0;break}g||n.push(t)}else n.push(t);if(localStorage.setItem("userAnswer",JSON.stringify(n)),l===r.answer&&p++,s++,s<a.length){o();let g=document.getElementById("question").innerText,u="",q=localStorage.getItem("userAnswer",l);if(q){let f=JSON.parse(q);for(let h=0;h<f.length;h++)if(f[h].question==g){u=f[h].answer;break}}document.getElementById(u).checked=!0}else b()}else e==null&&alert("Please select an answer!")}function v(){if(s--,s>=0){o();let e=document.getElementById("question").innerText,c="",r=localStorage.getItem("userAnswer",l);if(r){let t=JSON.parse(r);for(let n=0;n<t.length;n++)if(t[n].question==e){c=t[n].answer;break}}document.getElementById(c).checked=!0}else s<0&&alert("You reached first question of the topic!")}function b(){document.getElementById("main").innerHTML=`<h2>Quiz Completed!</h2>
    <p>Your score is: ${p}/${a.length}</p>`;let e=document.createElement("button");e.innerHTML="Go Back",e.addEventListener("click",()=>{location.reload()}),document.getElementById("main").append(e)}o()}
